What's up, Kaden? Let's go with the
obvious here. I mean, you were just here
for the local proday. You're, I'm
assuming, 20-ish minutes from us right
now. How does this feel?
>> It's surreal. I mean, growing up going
to Lucas Oil with all my family. Uh,
watching Pton Manning and all the
greats. It's uh definitely a dream come
true.
>> What jersey you got on now?
>> The Pton Manning Super Bowl jersey. Know
I had to wear it,
>> James. Go ahead.
>> Yeah, I'm about to say I feel like you
have to wear that, right? It's a
Cardinal son if you don't. Um, but I
know
>> Kaden, congrats on being drafted to, I
guess, the hometown team for you. Um,
how much contact did you have with the
Colts throughout the pregab process? And
then secondly, what do you think you can
bring to an NFL team?
>> Yeah. So, I mean, just from the start
talking with JT, my former team at Ohio
State, and getting with Coach Hobs, and
just everybody in that facility, uh,
sorry, you guys got me?
>> Yeah, we're good.
>> All right. And just being able to talk
to everybody in that facility. Yeah, I
mean, it's really just been a connection
that I've always wanted and uh just
meeting Chris Boward when I was a high
schooler, it was something that was
always going to be a dream come true and
something that I wish I could have had
sooner, but I obviously love being able
to have this opportunity.
>> Go ahead.
>> Yeah. When we talked at Combine, you
said like it was a dream come true to be
working out at Lucas Oil after being I
mean is this just the next step or was
this really hard to envision that this
might actually take place?
>> Um I feel like this is just the next
step in my career and I can't wait to do
the most with it and uh I just can't
wait to be able to do it in a city that
I grew up in and uh just to be able to
do it for all the people around me that
always believed in me and uh just to be
so close around them to do it too.
>> You're in Greenwood now? Yes, sir. I'm
in uh Greenwood, Indiana, 20 minutes
down the road. How
>> I mean family. What kind of a gathering
did you have? Do you have
>> Yeah. So, for us, it was just all
family. We have a big family background
and uh obviously all Colts fans and uh
we're just happy to be here and uh happy
it's so close to home.
>> Jake, go ahead.
>> Yeah. So, you really burst on the scene
last year in the your first year
starting uh with with JT coming here to
the Colts, 11 sack, 16 TFLs. What would
you say like what are your defining
traits? Like how did you get to be so
productive right away?
>> Um it's from learning from guys like JT
and uh all my other great defensive ends
from Ohio State. I knew what it took to
be a great guy at Ohio State and what it
took to be a great athlete and a great
defensive end to go there. And I knew
that if I could just make the most of it
and just to not let my opportunity slip
that I'd be the best version of myself
and to go out there and compete and just
make the most of it.
>> Kevin,
>> uh Kaden, uh was that a jersey just out
of the closet? Is that something you
used to rock as a kid?
>> Yeah, this is something that I've had
for a while as a Colts fan growing up
and obviously it's one of the goats from
Indianapolis and uh obviously I always
had it in the back of my closet.
Stylistically, how would you kind of
describe your game? It seemed like you
moved a little bit around uh with
Patricia taking over.
>> Yeah, obviously Coach Patricia is
obviously one of the great things that I
always cherish to have in college as my
senior year. Obviously, we had a great
defense coming back. We had great
playmakers all over the field as you've
guys seen from this weekend. and uh just
being able to compete with them and just
being a band of brothers out there. I
feel like we were always put in the best
positions to show what we could showcase
and I feel like it just helped us all be
the great best players that we could be
out there.
>> Abby, go ahead.
>> Kayen, congratulations. You've won two
high school state championships at Lucas
Oil. You've played at Lucas Oil for the
Big 10 title. As a fan though, do you
have any standout memories from being in
the stands there? Um, it's all the way
from being a little kid going to the
combines and just being able to watch
all these great players before me. I
mean, I was a Dwight Freeny and Robert
Matthysse fan growing up. That's the two
defensive ends that got me to want to
play this position. So, it's really not
one. It's really just everything that
I've grown up seeing and growing up
watching. It's been honestly a surreal
moment to be able to learn from those
guys and watch those guys growing up and
now be able to go play in the same shoes
that they were in. It's honestly just a
dream come true.
We'll just do just a few more. Nathan,
go ahead.
>> Um, obviously knowing so much about this
uh Colts roster, their makeup, who
they've got on the depth chart at the
moment as a lifelong fan in uh how how
do you feel like you can best impact
this team with the skills that you bring
to the table um just coming into this
summer? Yeah, I feel like I'm somebody
that you can put anywhere out there and
it's going to be productive. I'm the
type of guy that's going to work his
tail off in practice and he's going to
do whatever opportunity he gets and make
the most of it. And I feel like I'm
going to bring this edge to the
defensive end room and just the whole D
line room and that we're going to
compete together. Obviously, I know JT's
already there and he's has the same
mindset as me, so we're going to bounce
off each other and we're going to make
everybody else around us just the best
versions of themselves.
And last question, James.
>> Not a very serious question, but with
you coming back home, do you have to get
your own place now? Can you still stay
at your parents or how does that work?
>> I don't know. At this moment, I got to
figure it out and uh just play it one
day at a time. And I guess we'll see. I
heard a lot of players live up in the
Noblesville area. So, I might might have
to make the move to the north side.
>> All right. Appreciate it, man.
[laughter]
>> Actually, we'll go just one more with
Jake.
>> Yeah. So, obviously we all see the
videos of people celebrating at their
houses when they're drafted. Your
parents and your family are going to be
proud regardless, but like what was the
reaction from your family to see you
staying here?
>> Um, honestly, at first getting drafted
was the goal, and obviously we're very
happy about that. And then the icing on
the cake is definitely being back home
in Indianapolis. It was honestly their
favorite teams growing up. So seeing
their son go there was definitely a very
special moment for them and I'm glad
that I can make that happen for them and
I'm glad that I can do it for myself to
be able to come back here in the city of
Indianapolis. Obviously I left for
college and just to be able to come back
and to provide for this city and just to
be able to be a player that hopefully
everybody enjoys watching and uh I can
make the most out of my career here.